felissimo.com.cn 2018-08-17

# Privacy Policy | FELISSIMO

FELISSIMO'S PRIVACY POLICY

### Felissimo's Philosophy Regarding Protection of Personal Information

Felissimo is a direct marketing company, which produces various kinds of goods, services and projects, and delivers them directly to our customers, aiming to create a happy society through our business activities. As part of our operations and the operations of our related companies, we gain certain types of information about our users through our Website. Your Personal Information is important to us, and we consider proper management and protection of that information essential to our business activities and social responsibility. Thus, we have established the following Policy Regarding Protection of Personal Information, as one of the policies under the comprehensive management system IMS in our company, in connection with this Website.

### Felissimo's Policy Regarding Protection of Personal Information

  1. We will comply with the laws and guidelines established by the Japanese Government regarding our collection and handling of Personal Information. In addition, we will establish a Personal Information management system to appropriately protect your information.
  2. When we use or acquire Personal Information, we will specify the purpose for its use. We will not use Personal Information that we have acquired, in a manner that exceeds the scope necessary for achievement of its specified purpose (i.e., we will not use Personal Information for any other unstated purpose). We will take appropriate management action in order to prevent use for purposes other than those specified.
  3. We will collect and use Personal Information as set forth below in the section regarding "the protection and handling of customers' Personal Information," and will only use or share your Personal Information with third parties when (a) we believe you have consented to such sharing or use, (b) the use or sharing is reasonably necessary to offer and deliver our services and products at the Website or in the marketplace, or (c) if we are ordered or obligated to do so by law. For example, we will use or share Personal Information in order to process payments and deliver orders to you, or to send you direct mail or emails about your order(s) or the Website.
  4. If you have a complaint or inquiry about your Personal Information, please contact us; we have procedures in place to promptly investigate and respond to inquiries or complaints we receive.
  5. Your Personal Information is kept in files that are reasonably inaccessible by persons outside our company. Access within the company is generally limited to the employees who have a need to know such information.
  6. We will, from time to time, review our systems regarding the protection of Personal Information and may update our procedures and technology to help protect it.

Established: July 1, 2004  
Amended: August 1, 2013

Felissimo Corporation  
Kazuhiko Yazaki, Representative Director and President

### Disclosures Based on Private Information Protection Law

Felissimo complies with the Private Information Protection Law and other related regulations (Regulations below), and administers the personal information securely by taking appropriate measures.

**1\. Purposes for utilizing the personal information**

Felissimo utilizes the names, addresses, telephone numbers, date of birth, e-mail addresses, etc. collected from customers for the following purposes.  
Felissimo will not utilize the collected information other than for its intended purpose unless consent has been given by the individual beforehand or the matter falls under Regulations.

(1) Handle orders of Felissimo product/services, delivery, payment, etc., and fulfill and manage the order received.

(2) Mail catalogs introducing Felissimo products/services, promotional samples, direct mail, etc.

(3) Mail catalogs, promotional samples, direct mail, etc. from business-partner companies as determined appropriate by Felissimo.

(4) Request for participation in surveys to develop, and improve products and services

(5) Conduct marketing research to create statistical data while respecting the security of personal information to better grasp market trends and understand our customers.

(6) Conduct business and services by companies consigned by Felissimo.

(7) Conduct management of credit, payment, collection by companies consigned for transactions with Felissimo.

(8) Respond to your opinions and requests.

**2\. Disclosure of personal information (A)**

Felissimo will not disclose personal information to a third party for reasons other than listed below:

(1) If an individual has beforehand given consent. 

(2) If based on the Regulations 

(3) In the case of an emergency if the loss of human life, bodily injuries, assets are at stake and it is difficult to receive consent from the individual.

(4) If the personal information in part or in its entirety is necessary to complete its intended purpose.

(5) In the case of business succession such as joint venture, etc. personal information will be disclosed to the new entity.

(6) In the case of adverse consequence to meet operational intent, Felissimo or the consigned vendor/s will cooperate with national or local government agencies on matters set forth in the Regulations rather than receive consent from individual/s.

**3\. Disclosure of personal information (B)**

Felissimo may disclose personal information it collects to third parties to complete its intended purposes. If Felissimo determines to use a consignee, Felissimo will enter into an agreement to protect the security of personal information, and appropriately manage and oversee it in the course of its business.

**4\. Disclose, change, and stop usage of personal information**

Felissimo will disclose, change, and stop usage of personal information other than for reasons below:

① The personal information that Felissimo collects will be processed except to quickly disclose, change, suspend usage (below indicated as “disclose”) if:

(1) The identity of the individual cannot be confirmed.

(2) The minimally necessary information for business operation is lacking.

(3) The rights or profits of other customers or third party are jeopardized.

(4) If Felissimo determines inappropriateness for any other reasons.

② In processing disclosure, handling fee may be incurred.

③ (Contact information regarding inquiry of Personal Information)

**5\. Other**

① To conduct its operational intent using the collected personal information, Felissimo may disclose matter and process them without prior notice.

② Please read about Felissimo’s principles and policies regarding the protection of personal information on our website (<https://www.felissimo.co.jp/>).

③ To provide services on the website, cookies, web beacon, and other similar technology may be utilized.

Please click [here](https://www.felissimo.co.jp/other/cookie.cfm) for further information on the utilization of cookies for targeted advertising regarding interests and activities of individuals.

**6\. Company and person in charge of personal information protection and management**

Felissimo Corporation  
Personal Information Protection Manager

Special Provision (Regarding GDPR)

If you register as a member of Felissimo Global from a EU country, you are a target of EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and please read the following content.

1\. Once you registered in our site (as a member of Felissimo Global), it implies that you agree your personal data to be transferred to other countries in which the Personal Data Ordinance may not be the same as that in your own country. Felissimo complies with the applicable regulations and carries out proper measures in order to protect the personal data of the site users (member of Felissimo Global).

2\. Regardless of any content listed above, to purchase products and enjoy services at our site, you must be 16 years old or above. Those who are under 16 should ask parents or guardian to use the site on behalf of them.

3\. Felissimo complies with the EU General Data Protection Regulation（GDPR）and appoints Data Protection Officer and EU representative.  
Contact of Data Protection Officer (DPO): info_gc@felissimo.co.jp  
Contact of EU representative: info_gc@felissimo.co.jp

4\. Felissimo complies with the applicable regulation, makes sure there is no abuse or leakage of personal data of the site users (members of Felissimo Global), and maintains the correctness of all personal data. When accessing and transferring the personal data, we encrypt the data and set data access restrictions. Only the essential people who perform the relative tasks will be allowed to manage the data.

《Regarding the use of Cookies and Opt-out》   
Felissimo and our engaged internet service providers (including marketing, analyzing, CS support partners) use cookies or similar tools to collect the browsing statistics of our site. Felissimo may get those statistic reports from the providers in terms of individual data and aggregated data.

If you access our site with a browser permitting cookies, this implies you want to use the services of our site and agree Felissimo to use cookies in order to provide services from the site. 

Felissimo uses several categories of cookies for different functions like Shopping Bag, Favorite List and My Page. You can control the use of cookies in the browser setting or operating system. Please note that by disabling certain categories of cookies, some functions and features may not be available.

Felissimo contracts with service providers to place ads on websites owned by third parties. Felissimo and advertising partners may use cookies to collect your browsing history in order to deliver interest-based content and advertisements to you. If you do not want us to use your information in this field, please click [here](https://www.felissimo.co.jp/int/s/cookie) and we will stop delivering the interest-based ads (IBA) to you.

Please note that only IBA will be stopped. Other advertisements will be displayed as usual.
